Not only as a female but also as a hair stylist there's nothing I hate more personally than hearing my precious tool hit the ground.
I'm Laura Gibson, beauty expert and I'm here today to talk to you about curling irons, not only curling irons but your battery operated curling iron.
It's like any other curling iron.
You have your shell, your rod, but no cord.
That's the best part about it.
You can take it almost anywhere.
You can take it camping, Europe, different outlets.
Even better, less space in your bag when you go to travel.
The way the economy is now, that's an extra twenty five dollars for that little space.
Use it just like any other curling iron.
Open, and then curl it, let it go and voila, that's all there is to it.
I'm Laura Gibson, beauty expert and take care of your tools.